all right well I've been sitting at my
desk kind of putting off starting this
stream for about the last 15 minutes but
I guess I'm just gonna get on with it so
we kind of talked about this on land
show but there's been a little bit of
drama and then as of today there's been
more drama around Linus Media Group -
tech tips me personally whatever sort of
whatever entity you want to focus your
Ire at running out and copyright striking
other content creators and so I typed
myself up some notes here to hopefully
address this and lay it to rest once and
for all so when it comes to I guess the
first thing I want to do is sort of ask
our community the broader YouTube
community in general just people ask
them to try to think critically anytime
they run up against some kind of
accusation like I'm not saying that you
know all accusations should be dismissed
I'm just also not saying that all
accusations should be taken entirely at
face value and then just run with so
here are some of the questions that I
would probably ask myself if I were to
encounter any sort of any sort of drama
not just YouTube drama who are the
stakeholders here what do they
individually stand to lose or gain what
is the actual solution to this problem
who has the power to enact that solution
where could I find more information
about what's going on
is it worth the time that I'm investing
to find that information in the case of
the particular thing that's going on
where people are receiving content ID
notifications not to be confused with a
copyright strike I'll talk about that
later
but in the case of people receiving
these Content ID notification
has anyone have these people actually
contacted - Media Group about it
directly we actually have a contact us
email on our corporate website we also
have a contact us email for a Linus tech tips
specifically on our YouTube channel that
stuff does get monitored on business
days mind you like this is my long
weekend it's family day here in British
Columbia but I'm dealing with this
instead of doing what I would really
much rather be doing um here are some
here are some other questions we can ask
ourselves whenever we encounter drama
what else is already posted in the
comments on the video is there something
with a ton of upvotes that sort of
answers my question am I being
manipulated to join a crusade is the is
it based on ignorance or is there some
kind of agenda so those are all the just
general questions that I'd really like
people to ask themselves whenever they
are sort of called to join a cause with
the most important ones I think being
who are the stakeholders what do they
stand to lose and gain what is the
actual solution and what could or has
already been done about it and then for
for myself personally this has been
there's been kind of frustrating
offensive hurtful I'm you know there's a
bunch of different words for it because
the the questions that I'd like you guys
to ask yourselves about me and and my
company specifically is is Linus Media
Group some kind of monster that's not
still run by real people who give a
as opposed to you know some nameless
faceless corporation like yeah we're
we're on the bigger side especially of
tech YouTube channels but that doesn't
mean that like we've worked hard to get
here it's not like it we got there by
being you know jerks or anything we
haven't you know engaged in market
manipulation or any other unfair
competitive practice you know another
question to ask yourself is is the
behavior that Linus media groups being
accused of or - personally is being
accused of is that in character is Linus
Pro censorship does he silence criticism
is there is that behavior that anyone
has actually encountered
from us in the past and if we haven't
then you know is it may be worthwhile to
give the benefit of the doubt
so all right now we're we're past sort
of the the preface to the stream so
let's get into some of the points that
I've more completely prepared I was like
sitting inside my car having sort of
scrolled soot scroll through some
comments on the forum some comments on
YouTube I'm trying to figure out sort of
what I need to address so I wrote myself
up kind of a little script here but of
course it's all in it's all my own words
just a few guys see me kind of looking
down it's because I'm looking at this at
the screen I'm just dreaming this awful
webcam at my house so here's the deal
look I think I just shook the camera
sorry about that guys so I'm not gonna
be naming any of the individuals that
are stirring the pot here because my
general policy when it comes to public
drama is one of zero acknowledgement
like if there's a legitimate grievance
no problem get in touch we'll do our
best to solve it I think we have a
pretty good reputation not just among
viewers but within the creator community
as being an organization like not just
me of course it's there's 20 plus people
that work at Linus Media Group but being
an organization that just generally
cares about fixing problems and doing
the right thing I mean an example of
sort of our zero acknowledgement like
you you just you won't you won't hear
from us about this stuff I feel like I
can bring up this one now because it's
sort of not relevant anymore but we had
an issue with totalbiscuit at one point
where after having a relationship in the
past we had him on the way on show at
one point he put me and Luc personally
on blast publicly over something that
was posted by a user on our forum and
that was instead of contacting either me
or Luc directly and the really bizarre
thing about that was that I know a
hundred percent that he had my email
since he had no problem asking for and
even receiving multiple times text
or from me and then like when I reached
out directly rather than replying on
Twitter because I'm not going to do that
when I reached out directly like yo WTF
can you retract your comments publicly
cuz that's really unfair like this this
is a user comment on our forum you
didn't even you didn't even contact us
and asked us to have it dealt with he
basically said and I'm paraphrasing here
I didn't feel like pulling up the email
cuz it was really annoying he basically
said like I don't get why you expect me
to reach out to you directly we're not
friends and you need to moderate your
forum better our subreddit is moderated
you're responsible for the content on
your forum I'm kind of sitting here
going what are you even talking about
like at its peak your subreddit was a
small fraction of our forum we have like
a really really debt it like massive
shout-out to our forum moderators we
have a dedicated community over there
and it's a lot of work what they do to
keep the Linus tech tips forum running
they're amazing they do a great job and
you go after my moderators who tell me
they're you know they're subpar just
because someone posted something that
was offensive to you but not necessarily
even against our Community Guidelines
actually don't remember exactly what the
post was but like yeah he went on the
list you never saw another
acknowledgement from Linus media group
because that's that's the way that's the
way to me things should work that's the
way my engagement with people on the
internet works because that's how my
human relationships works so whether
it's my household my friends my family
my company
these are drama-free zones and if you
can't abide by those rules if you can't
stay drama-free then I am well within my
rights to completely ignore you and the
funny thing is like like we've we try to
like we do that in an effort to try and
take the high road and a lot of the time
I feel like we end up looking bad
because other people get their shots in
at us and we just we just never return
fire like it's not like I've never had
personal you know beef to use the lingo
I suppose with other content creators
but here's the thing I guarantee you
don't know who they are because anyone
that I have actually feuded with
publicly like Jays two cents or Steve
from gamers Nexus trying to beat their
benchmark scores or Paul and Kyle
ripping their award away from them at
the end of scrapyard Wars or Louis
Rossman with the whole you know baking a
GPU and oh wow you really shouldn't do
that Linus he said it a little more
colorfully than that but the point is
the point is anyone that I have publicly
feuded with or beefed with I both like
and respect in private like these are
people that I would sit down and have a
drink without a trade show not that I
drink but yeah I can have water they can
have something stronger whatever works
for them I'm not actually monitoring
chat right now cuz I'm reading my thing
but hopefully the stream is like working
properly and stuff you know it seems
like it's fine so back to the question
of agendas this is the most important
thing to think about again I'm not gonna
be naming any names for reasons that
I've explained already but I will say
that at least one individual out there
who has drawn attention to the matter of
these Linus tech tips Content ID flags
okay so this person rather than simply
disputing the claims and don't bother
speculating about who it is because
there's so many people that are
complaining about it at this point and
I'll get into why there's a bunch of
people complaining about these Content
ID flags and why that's happening in a
little bit but there's so many people
you're probably not going to guess the
one that I'm talking about which is the
only reason that I'm allowing myself to
allude to this but at least one of the
people rather than simply disputing the
Content ID claims per the standard
operating procedure took their problem
public rather than just emailing me and
I know that at least one of these people
more than one actually more than one of
these people have my contact
information my personal contact
information from applying for a job at
Linus Media Group in the past one that
they obviously didn't get so I
disappointed I'm disappointed in the way
that some people have handled this
without just talking to me when they
obviously have my contact info which
hasn't changed in the entire time that
Linus Media Group has exist existed and
I'm I I never win myself any friends
when I say stuff like this but that's
not really the goal of today's stream
I'm I'm a little disappointed in the
community you know not necessarily over
on the forum by and large the folks over
there have been more understanding and
have dug a little deeper for the facts
before raising their pitchforks but the
the YouTube viewer community more
broadly I've been disappointed in the
way that some individuals have just
assumed that I'm some kind of you know
wielder of you know the copyright been
hammer without any regard for fair use
or for smaller creators or that I'm some
kind of like anti-competitive asshole
like based on what evidence is this
assumption being made like am I
automatically evil for a problem with an
automated system that I don't control a
problem that was brought to my attention
literally on Friday morning or do we
live in a place where you are guilty and
guilty until proven innocent maybe
there's another way of saying that you
should be assumed innocent until proven
guilty
why don't we assume the best of people
until we are presented with
incontrovertible evidence that they are
actually acting out of malice so so so
then with that in mind what I'm gonna do
is I'm gonna take all of the vitriol
that I've been getting over the last
couple of days and I'm going to assume
that everyone who is dishing it out did
it out of ignorance rather than out
of some kind of ill-will so I want the
rest of the stream to be more about
educating people rather than sort of
complaining about the situation all
right
so someone on our forum actually did a
better job of this then I probably could
have it's an excellent post so what I'm
gonna do is I'm gonna read it out so
that you guys can fully understand the
difference between a Content ID claim
and a copyright strike because they are
spectacularly different so it was posted
by spotty over on our forum actually I
can hopefully this works I'm gonna
screen share with you guys yeah it looks
like it's working cool so spotty posted
in response to someone else you seem to
be misinformed there is a huge
difference between a copyright claim and
it take down notice resulting in a
copyright strike copyright claims which
was what happened to one of the people
that made a video are often actually as
far as I know they just are an automatic
process where content actually no no no
no no that's correct
often not always because we actually ran
into one that was on purpose a little r1
that was manual a little while ago we
included a few notes of a song in the
the cheap 4k TV video the video has
since been edited and we've got
monetization re-enabled on it but ya
know it can be manual so an often
Odyssey like I said spotty did it better
than I could often automatic process
where Content ID detects that a portion
of your copyrighted content has appeared
in another video on YouTube and will
issue a copyright claim on the video so
that video remains public and viewable
not all these viewable everywhere
because sometimes it will be blocked off
in like certain regions per the
copyright holders guidelines however
what happens after that point is that
any ad revenue generated by the video
may be redirected to the original
copyright holder so there's no actual
punishment for the channel when when
this Content ID copyright claim is made
against them they only lose the revenue
for the video
okay so now that we've got all that
obviously this is not a perfect solution
because what if someone
what if someone submitted a mash-up of
youtuber reaction videos and then all
you know nine of the people in the 3x3
tile of reacting to whatever it is are
eight I guess it would because the
original content would be in the middle
what if they all submitted Content ID
claims well I don't know how you split
something anyways I don't think it's
actually about granular so it's
obviously not a perfect system and
there's a lot of room for false
positives but there's no punishment for
the channel there's no long term impact
just the revenue and just on that
particular video now copyright strikes
or takedown notices so this is this is
like DMCA stuff
that's what the verge did to Kyle okay
so that's when the copyright owner
manually issues a legal notice that the
video is infringing on their copyright
and they demand that the video be
removed from the platform so the channel
then receives a strike against their
channel which comes with punishments
such as losing the ability to livestream
just one strike and you can't livestream
anymore and can even come with the
potential to be demoted in terms of
YouTube's YouTube serving your content
to people though I don't think that's
ever actually been confirmed and then
after multiple copyright strikes so
remember this is DMCA takedowns the
channel can be removed completely I
think it's three right before don't
quote me on that Ben so that that's
really different and that is not what is
happening right now so what's happening
is Content ID claims and what is not
happening is manual DMCA takedowns so
Content ID claims are handled by YouTube
algorithmically
so our MCN full screen is making sure
that people aren't real plotting our
videos because that does actually happen
a lot and that way we don't have to pull
all that crap down and go through it
manually fill out a bunch of annoying
paperwork just if people reload our
videos we just take the Adsense fine who
cares no big deal the only times that we
have issued DMCA takedowns are for
people who are up
loading content that is supposed to be
on other sites such as hold on mixed
messaging oh I didn't mean to do that
Thank You Nick um there we go so let's
go back to that how was I talking about
right okay so there was something that I
wanted to add so Content ID on top of it
not having any long-term ramifications
for the channel aside from just losing
the revenue on that video if you believe
for whatever reason that that Content ID
claim is not valid
you can dispute it and I'm actually
gonna walk you guys through the process
for how to dispute a Content ID claim
I'll show you I'm gonna dispute one on
my channel right now if you dispute it
in a timely manner it actually doesn't
even affect the monetization of the
video either so it's some period of days
like you don't have to do it ten minutes
after you get it but I also wouldn't
wait for a week or a month or whatever
else but if you do it right away then
there is literally no impact whatsoever
other than to help train the YouTube
algorithm so let's go ahead and fire up
here we go hopefully I am doing all this
correctly yeah seems fine okay so let's
fire up a video here we've actually
gotten a ton of Content ID claims over
the last probably I'd say week or so
including some from our own channels
against our own channels just because I
is my belief that they have made some
changes to the Content ID system making
a little bit more sensitive it's again
my belief I don't have any proof of this
but that it is due to the ongoing
chapter 13 stuff that's going on in the
EU but I've disputed most of them so
you'll see that most of these aren't
really that new so this was streamed in
last November includes copyrighted
content so we go ahead and we click on
this okay
it says ads might appear on your video
copyrighted content was found in your
video the claimant is allowing their
content to be used in your YouTube video
however ads might appear on it if you
agree with these conditions you don't
have to do
anything monetized by claimant you can
use the copyrighted content your video
but ads might appear in your video okay
so we can learn more just go ahead and
let me learn some more what is a Content
ID claim if you upload a video that
contains copyright protected material
you could end up with a Content ID claim
companies that are music movies TV shows
video games another copyright protected
material content owners can set content
had to eat a block material from YouTube
when a claim is may they can also allow
the video to remain live on YouTube with
ads in those cases the revenue goes to
the copyright owners of the claimed
content okay am I in trouble
probably not in most cases getting a
Content ID claim isn't a bad thing for
your YouTube channel it just means hey
we found some content your video that's
owned by someone else it's up to the
copyright owners to decide whether or
not others can reuse their original
material in many cases they allow their
content to be used in YouTube videos in
exchange for having ads run on those
videos these ads may play before the
video or during it bla bla bla alright
they can mute it they can block certain
platforms they can block a video what
can I do about this claim if you get a
Content ID claim there are a few
different things you can do depending on
the situation you can do nothing if you
agree but yeah I probably shouldn't use
that you can leave it and you can always
change your mind later you can remove
the music so that's cool you can swap
the music you can share revenue if
you're a member of the YouTube Partner
Program you may be able to share revenue
with the music rights owner I actually
did not know about that it's kind of
neat you can dispute the claim if you
have the required rights to use the
copyright protected content your video
or if you think the system has somehow
misidentified your video you may dispute
the claim so how to dispute a claim you
go to let's go back to where we were
okay oh yeah first we can check and see
what exactly it is so in this case it
was oh it was a trailer for some Pokemon
thing or other oh we were doing live
commentary so yes this is copyrighted
content but it's a trailer which is
generally considered to be for
promotional purposes it's very unlikely
that a copyright holder would be mad at
you for playing their trailer and
talking about it that's kind of like
what the point of them is also where
we're commenting on it that's pretty
pretty well established to be a fair use
use case for it so we're gonna file a
dispute
I believe this copyright claim is not
valid
here's a few options I beheld the cd/dvd
or bought the song online by the way if
you click that if that's your reason
you're wrong
I gave credit in the video if you click
that that's your reason you're wrong the
video is my original content I own all
the rights yep
sometimes it just Flags random crap we
we actually had a claim against an actor
April Fool's video we uploaded where it
was just a case lying in the rain and it
was just the sound of rain and there was
a claim that that we had used someone
else's rain sound effect we were like yo
let's no it's just our microphone
sitting on the porch no so that was that
was all our original content here's
another one I have license for
permission to use this material okay my
use of the content meets the legal
requirements for fair use or fair
dealing under applicable copyright laws
that's the one we're going to use here
or the content is in the public domain
and not eligible for copyright
protection so these are all the reasons
you can say that that it's fine to use
it so here we go in the case of the
heaven benchmark which was what I think
a lot of people are getting flagged on
we don't own that and as far as I know
Unigine gives zero FS about people
uploading their benchmark content
they've never talked to us about it and
we've got probably hours of it in our
videos which is probably why other
people are getting claims because like
we uploaded it a lot and quite early on
and it's just it you have to submit
these reports otherwise the system can't
fix itself now I can understand where a
lot of people whoops
I just hit a hotkey that's not a thing
good there we go I can understand why a
lot of people would find the wording of
what would be the correct response here
kind of scary
my use of the content meets the legal
requirements for fair use or fair
dealing under applicable copyright laws
that's a scary thing to click because it
feels like you should probably consult a
lawyer before you click on something
like that
but that's not necessarily the case you
know what I would say is make sure that
you at the very least I would say that
at the at the very least you should you
know probably read up on what went down
with h3h3 productions and that person
they made a reaction video of a lot of
good material there there was a lawyer
that actually did a bunch of content
sort of around that very educational I
would like at least gogo read up on that
but no not not necessarily I mean fair
fair use in some cases is pretty
cut-and-dried whereas in other cases
yeah you you might actually end up in
court trying to defend it so a lot of
the time yeah it's probably better off
to just leave it which is why you'll see
we do actually have here if I go back to
the dashboard oh no I'm not gonna go
back to the dashboard yet you know what
I'm gonna finish my I'm gonna finish my
my dispute here okay
I believe this is not valid because my
use blah blah blah fair use etc yep
continue I'm quite sure about this a
visual content please explain briefly we
are commenting on this trailer I believe
this is fair use I have in good faith
etc etc etc thank you I understand well
that's my name continue and we can
submit our dispute yes yes I'm sure so
the process takes about 30 seconds and
if you if you do these things you're
actually helping them make the Content
ID system better because if they get a
bunch of disputes then they can go back
and they can say oh right okay so that's
probably not right let's go ahead and
get that updated um so there you go
dispute in progress
typically these take a couple of days
for my experience but that is that is
the entire process hopefully that was
illuminating for y'all I think there was
a thing I said I was going to get back
to I forget what it was but let's go
back to my notes here yeah actually you
know what no I think that's pretty much
all I have to say on the subject if
anyone out there did get a Content ID
claim from - Media Group - tech tips any
of its affiliated whatever unless you're
actually just reloading our videos which
you're not supposed to do I would say
just dispute it the worst thing that
could possibly happen is we could say
nope we dispute your dispute
we disagree I never done that it's just
not really a thing people upload all
kinds of like highlight reels or silly
reuses of of limas media group content
you know set to songs or like whatever
we love that kind of stuff we love our
community memeing it up we we consider
ourselves a fairly internet savvy
company and not just like the internet
but also just oh all right Nick yeah
thanks Nick Nick told me what I was what
I was showing I was gonna show a thing
that wasn't worth disputing but we
consider ourselves not just like how the
internet works a V would also internet
culture savvy and we recognize that you
know memes and discussion about us is
it's just it's good if people want to
just like have fun with us and engage
with us that way it's great I've gotten
many many and everything from smile to
full-on laugh from the kinds of things
that our community has done with our
content and I love it so yeah I just
submit a dispute it'll probably be fine
so Nick reminded me what I had said I
was going to do I was going to show some
of the copyright notices that I
considered not worth disputing some of
these were left this one was left in
here just because it's like Rancho
Rancho doesn't really like make any
money on Adsense anyway like after the
first week or so it doesn't get any view
so what am I like what am i bothering
for it's like it's not worth the 30
seconds it takes me to dispute the
stupid thing but some of these I left
because there is actually potential
legal ramifications if I dispute it and
they decide they don't like my dispute
and they they want to they want to go to
court over whether it's fair you so this
I think is an example of that the
fallout 4 ultimate bomb case build log
so here we used some kind of classical
music apparently yeah so this is like
music stuff which from our experience is
super complicated because there's
different copyrights for the actual
sheet
music itself and the performance and it
varies from country to country and we
were just like this was around the time
that we were just like you know what
screw it we're just gonna like pay the
thousands and thousands of dollars that
it costs to subscribe to a service like
Warner Chappell and we're just gonna
gonna invest in having music for our oh
I'm parent Lee I'm not showing you guys
the screen right now
sorry Thank You Nick what would I do
without you're my guardian angel so here
you go
so they'll fall out for ultimate bomb
build there you go so here's a bunch of
performances we were just like you know
what we're not gonna we're not gonna
deal with that we're just gonna we're
just gonna spend a lot the new one we're
on now is like evac forget which one it
is it's like even better than the
warner/chappell libraries we were using
but it's like I was like 15 grand a year
so I'm stupid like that's amazing how
much it costs to to do things properly
so this is an example of one that we're
just we're just gonna leave if they want
the you know a few hundred bucks or
whatever then I guess they're they're
welcome to it going back there's just
like some older stuff that I just didn't
bother with as well but I'm glad I
didn't bother with all of them because
at least it means that I had this to
show you wonderful people how to dispute
a Content ID claim I guess right before
I go I should probably see if there's
any like chats or anything that I should
deal with
mostly just people being nice supportive
well that's kind of amazing
a couple people just want a summary of
the issue since they tuned in a little
bit later in this dream okay so
basically people have been getting
Content ID claims not to be confused
with copyright strikes from lions Media
Group they're from fullscreen on behalf
of Lynas Media Group these have been
false content ID matches a lot of them
on the heaven benchmark not although and
people think and a bunch of pitchforks
are being raised and torches and all
that that - Media Group is you know
trying to keep down smaller creators or
whatever totally not a thing not what
happened it's an automated system we
believe it's gotten some updates lately
and disputing Content ID claims is super
easy I showed earlier on this stream how
you do it as long as as you don't think
the original copyright holder doesn't
have a claim to it either it's pretty
safe to go ahead and just dispute those
things it's really not a lot that can go
wrong it has no long-term impact on your
channel so it's all good we just all
need to have less drama and you know
give people the benefit of the doubt if
we have a problem with them we need to
reach out from directly I'm actually
shockingly easy to get ahold of I do
ignore the vast majority of the tweets
that get sent to my handle just because
like the last time I opened the Twitter
app was on Friday when I was at work
because I don't actually Twitter because
I like it i twitter because it's my job
boo there's there's a there's a
bombshell confession you know if you
send it to my email the business
inquiries only email we can't we
actually cannot reply to every email
that comes to that we reply to the
business inquiries what we do do though
is read them all so if there's something
that we are getting a ton of messages
about then we will address it in some
other way I just mean we're easy to get
in touch with even if you don't
necessarily get a response and hopefully
we've demonstrated
so that's unless Nikki's got something
else urgent that he feels like I need to
address I'm not a legal professional
Thank You Nick
that's very very helpful for me to point
out to everyone that's all I've got to
say on the subject there's no doubt that
drama sells and I'm not above monetizing
the video you guys are watching right
now and my if I'm gonna get sucked into
this thing I might as well you know make
a couple of shekels and you know go buy
some new video games to play tonight
while I relax but I have zero appetite
for continuing to follow up on this
I'm only even making this as a
standalone video rather than addressing
it on the LAN show because the episode
of the LAN show from Friday which should
be up and contains my response to this
is still down due to a technical issue
on youtubes end so here we are
fortunately YouTube streaming worked for
me for a continuous however however long
we've been live right now which is great
and half an hour holy crap I've been
doing this for half an hour okay you
know what it's family day let me go
spend some time with my kids hopefully
you guys have a fantastic rest of your
weekend or long weekend or or whatever
else it is that you guys are up to see
ya