Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Please take your seats
if you haven't already.
The makers of this film wanted me
to address you before we proceed.
This is a film about sex,
more specifically sex addiction.
It is probably one of the strangest films
you will ever see.
I think, it will thrill you.
I know it will shock you.
It may even horrify you.
So, if any of you feel
that you cannot endure it,
please leave now.
Well, I warned you.
Oh, god.
Jake.
Jake, wake up.
You're not fooling anybody.
Do you hear it, Jake?
I know you can.
Isn't it beautiful?
Fuck, fuck, fuck, oh!
Where do you
think it's coming from?
Across the hall?
The floor above?
No, next door.
That's where it's coming from next door.
Jake, come on.
You know you can't sleep, not now.
Who you tryin' to fool?
Listen.
It's getting louder again.
Listen to it, Jake.
Oh, god.
It's like you're right
in there watching them.
You feel how hard your dick is?
Ah, go into the bathroom.
That's where it's the loudest.
That's it.
Doesn't that feel good?
Closer.
Closer, that's it.
Get right up against the wall.
Fuck, that's hot!
It's that couple next door.
I bet her pussy's so fucking wet.
Don't be jealous enjoy it, that's it.
It's beautiful.
Cum with them, that's it.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, god.
Time to start the night, Jake.
Time to start the night.
Jake, how are you?
I'm good.
I can't hear you?
I said I'm good.
Wait, I'm gonna come over there.
Where have you been?
I haven't seen you since you
helped me with my cabinets.
I've just been keeping busy.
Doing what?
Just things.
How's your sister?
She's good.
She's coming back tonight, actually.
That's great, you must be excited.
Yeah, I am.
Are you still in school?
We're on break.
Still?
I hate to do this to
you, I hate to be rude,
but I actually have a lot of
stuff to do, if you don't mind.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, it's really late, sorry.
You know, I'm sure you
have a really, really
long night ahead of you.
But if you have any time,
why don't you come by my
apartment and fuck me?
I'm sorry.
I know you're getting
ready to fuck your sister.
You know, she's a slut.
Jake.
Yeah.
I said why don't you come
by and visit me tomorrow?
I have a leaky pipe that I
could use some help with.
You know, how much I
don't like to call Felix.
Yeah, tomorrow I'll stop by.
Have a good night.
Okay, have a good night.
Jake, we left a
little bit of money for you,
and dad left you a gift.
Love, mom and dad.
Awe, isn't that nice, Jake?
Let's see what your dad got you.
Wow, look at that thing.
What are you gonna do with that, Jake?
Stop messing around.
Let's get started.
Hi, I'm calling
about the $200 special.
It's tonight only, right?
Yeah, I'm 21.
I live on 14th Street.
It's the Village East End.
Yeah, I live on the fifth floor, room 503.
Alright, see you soon, bye.
Hi.
Uh, you can come on in.
Thank you.
You can put, uh...
You can take your boots off
and sit down, if you want.
Thanks.
I'm Veronica.
I'm Jake, hi.
- Nice to meet you.
So.
Wanna get started.
I don't bite.
So, what do you want?
I'm not sure.
I wanna do everything to you.
Well, I'm fetish friendly.
Do you have any fetishes?
I want you to put your foot in my mouth.
Okay.
Does that feel good, baby brother?
Stop.
What's wrong?
Get on top of me.
Sure.
All right.
You're so good, Jake.
You're the best.
Spank me, Jake.
Spank me harder!
Harder!
Cum on my face.
Sorry, if I got your
bed a little bit messy.
Um, is that for me?
Oh, yeah, that's for you.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
What's the matter, Jake?
Wondering what games I'm playing with you?
Wondering why you're seeing
your sister during sex?
It's quite simple.
We need something more.
I'm talking about a greater high,
something so fucked up
but it feels so good.
Where are you going?
This won't do.
The usual's not gonna be enough anymore.
You're going to be disappointed.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I was wondering
if I could have a session?
Did you schedule an appointment?
No, but I have money.
How old are you?
22.
Can I see your ID?
Yeah.
All right.
Come on in.
Take your shoes off.
I take my money upfront.
It's the $100 special today only, right?
That's right.
Alright, baby, couple of ground rules
to go over before we get started.
This session is for one hour.
When the hour is over, you must go.
Um, as far as, me I'm open to anything,
golden showers, pegging,
everything is fair game to me.
You can pick your own safe word.
I don't want a safe word.
Baby, I think...
Trust me.
Alright, well, I wasn't expecting you,
so I have to get into custom.
But I'll be right back.
Make yourself at home.
Jake, what are you doing here?
Why waste your money?
This isn't good enough anymore.
She's not Molly, Jake.
Can't you see I'm trying to help you?
Can't you see what I'm trying to do?
I'm talking about something better.
I wouldn't do anything to hurt you, Jake.
You believe me, don't you, Jake?
Alright, have your fun.
But this won't change anything.
You'll see.
I'm not going away, Jake.
I promise you that.
Have you been a bad boy?
Yes, mistress.
Take your shirt off.
Throw it on the floor.
Yes, mistress.
Get on your knees.
So, you've been a bad boy?
Yes, mistress.
And you're a dirty little bitch,
who needs to be punished!
- Yes, mistress!
- Say it!
I'm a dirty little bitch,
who needs to be punished!
Good.
You don't mind this, do you?
You like it, don't you?
Oh, yeah.
Yes, mistress.
Ah, ah, ah.
Fucking pathetic.
Yes, mistress.
Yes, mistress, louder!
Yes, mistress!
Oh, I'm sorry does that hurt?
Does that hurt?
- Oh.
I'm gonna have fun with you.
Yes, mistress.
Yes, mistress, louder!
Yes, mistress!
- I can't fucking hear you,
you pathetic piece of shit.
Yes, mistress!
Are you ready to be punished, slave?
- Oh, yes, mistress!
- I can't fucking hear you!
Yes, mistress!
Hey, I'm sorry I couldn't get you off,
but you just didn't seem that into it.
It's all right.
BDSM isn't for everybody.
It wasn't my first time.
Bye.
See, Jake, what did I tell you?
We need something new, something more,
the ultimate high, your sister Jake.
You're supposed to pick her up, right?
That's perfect.
Come on go see your sister, Jake.
Jake.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Jake?
Yeah.
You don't remember us,
Elizabeth, Chris, Korab from school?
Oh, yeah.
How have you guys been?
Better than you, at
least by the looks of it.
Yeah, what the hell
happened to your eye, man?
Oh, it's a long story.
What are you guys up to though?
We were just
gonna go grab something.
You come with us.
I was about to...
I was about to go somewhere.
Come on.
Neither of you are gonna ask him
why he just blew us all off?
I mean, look, I don't wanna
start any shit in a restaurant,
but we have a right to know.
What do you wanna know?
We wanna know why you just
stopped coming to school?
Why you just dropped out
without telling anyone,
not your professors, not your friends,
not me, who I thought
was your best friend,
not even Monica, bro,
Monica, your fucking girlfriend?
It's one thing to treat us like dog shit,
but your girlfriend, that's fucked up.
And if neither of them
were gonna say anything,
then I had to let you know
how disrespectful that was
to the people that thought
they meant something to you.
I mean, I don't know
what you want me to say.
I mean, tell me at least you
had a good reason for all it.
All I can say is I had my reasons.
If that's not good enough,
I don't know what to tell you.
That's all you have to say?
I mean, I don't know
what you want me to say.
This fucking guy, man.
I don't know.
I don't know what you guys want me to say.
Are you okay?
I mean, yeah, my eye.
No, it's not just your eye.
Frankly, you look like shit.
What's the real reason you
dropped out of school, drugs?
I just wanted other things.
Hey, Jake.
I remembered this was your favorite.
Why don't you come lick it off me?
Jake.
Yeah.
Korab, was right.
Something happened to you.
Don't worry about them.
Don't worry about your
bitch of an ex, Jake.
Didn't you hear?
She's with some other guy.
You're different, Jake, embrace it.
Jake, don't.
Jake don't remember her.
Think about Molly.
Embrace the high.
Tell me a secret.
I feel like I'm the
luckiest guy in the world.
Awe.
Tell me a lie.
I don't think
you're the cutest boy I know.
Cute.
What's the matter with hot?
Come on cute's cute, and you're cute.
I mean, I guess, I'll take it.
Tell me a lie.
I don't
love you or your family.
You're not even trying.
What can I say, I'm a happy guy.
Tell me a secret.
I wanna have your kids.
Really?
Uh-huh.
How many will we have?
Let's see, um,
a boy.
Definitely.
Shut up.
A boy and two girls.
Three kids?
I mean, I guess, I better
get started on that boy.
It's so the brother can look
after his siblings, you know?
Or in my case the sister
look out for her brother.
That sounds good to me.
I'll be there.
Good, 'cause I wouldn't
want you anywhere else.
I don't know if I can
do this anymore, Jake.
What do you mean?
All you wanna do is watch porn.
I mean, we can't even make
love like a regular couple
because it doesn't get your off enough.
What's wrong with fucking with a porno
on in the background?
I'm just trying to spice things up.
That's my point.
You never used to call it fucking.
It was always making love.
Making love, fucking
what's the difference?
There is a difference, Jake.
You used to like making love to me,
and now all you wanna do is fuck.
Yeah, it's me Jake.
I know it's been a while.
Can I come see you?
I got a lot on my mind.
I think, you can help.
Alright, I'll be over soon.
Sorry about the mess.
It was my two siblings.
I share the room with them
till I get back on my feet.
No, that's fine.
So how the hell you been, man?
I haven't seen you in forever.
I'm actually not doin' so good.
Just about to ask you about your eye.
What happened, you got jumped
on the way here or what?
Oh, yeah, my eye it's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
You not back in the life?
Jake, come on, man.
How long?
Been back in for a while.
I should've known I haven't seen you
at the meetings in a while.
What you want me to sponsor
you back and get you in, what?
No, I was actually hoping you had
had something to sort me out.
Sort you out?
You mean like pills?
Yeah, I need something, man.
Let me see.
Now describe to me what's going on.
Well, it's like I can't
control my thoughts.
It's like my brain is trying
to get me to do crazier
and crazier sexual shit,
shit I would never do.
I can't get off otherwise.
Yeah, it's a sexual high.
The brain is a funny thing, my friend.
Here take this.
What is it?
It's some good shit.
I'm a hit it myself, and it's as small
as an everyday.
Yeah, but you haven't
told me what it is.
It's a form of psychedelic.
You'll see some weird shit.
But it'll stop your mind
from fuckin' with you
even for a little bit.
Yeah, listen, that's the
best I can do, my friend.
Alright, man, I really appreciate it.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
I don't have much money to pay you.
Man, don't worry about it.
This is on the house.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Now where you headed?
I was thinking about heading down to...
I was thinking headin' over to the Bowery.
The fucking bar.
Jake, why would you wanna go down there?
You know you only hurting yourself, right?
Hey, man, listen I
really do appreciate this,
the stuff, I mean.
It was good seeing you.
I think, I'm gonna be out though.
Alright,
Jake, take it easy man.
Don't be a stranger, okay?
All right.
Alright, thanks again.
Hey, Jake, you be safe, man.
Take care of yourself.
Doesn't that feel good, baby?
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the Talent Show.
I can see we have a packed house tonight.
Either way, let's get this
show on the road, huh?
I'm going to bring out your
first contestant of the evening.
Her talent is singing,
and she's recently single.
You know what that means
guys, especially you.
Please give a nice round
of applause for Ms. Molly.
Thank you.
One more time a nice round of applause
for the lovely Ms. Molly.
Singing about swinging.
Now who's our next lucky contestant?
How about you, sir?
Would you like to come on up
here and show us your talent?
What's your name?
It's Jake.
Jake.
Take it away.
How's everybody doin'?
I'm not really good at this sort of thing.
I'm not sure what I should do.
Do you sing?
No, I don't.
You don't have to sing.
What's your talent?
I don't really have one.
Sure you do.
Your cock.
Show them your cock.
It's why you're here, isn't it?
Ladies and gentlemen, once
again give it up for Jake.
Tough crowd, huh?
Listen, Jake.
Silence!
We have a consolation prize for you,
something that'll make
you feel a little better.
Come here, Jake.
Come to me.
Come on.
Come on, Jake.
You know you want to.
Come to me.
Hey, man, are you okay?
You seem a little spaced out.
Come with me there's
something I think you'll like.
How you ladies doin'?
What do we have here?
Who's this?
He's my friend?
Does he speak?
He's a little fucked up.
I don't know what drugs he took,
but he's not doin' too good.
He just needs you ladies to wake him up.
We can do that.
Right girls?
Definitely.
Against the wall.
Take off your jacket and your shirt.
See this whip.
We gonna use this on you.
Turn around.
How does that feel?
Feels good.
Is this what you want?
Yes.
Say it.
Yes!
You like being dominated by three women?
Yes, I do.
You like being our property?
Yes!
Good.
Now hit her.
Hit her now, slave.
Harder!
Now let's put him in his place.
You are weak.
Weak.
You are helpless.
Nobody can save you.
Look at him.
Hey, it's just me.
I guess you forget to
pick me up at the station.
Don't worry I won't tell mom.
I'm headed to the hotel to
unpack and get settled in.
You should definitely come
by later if you have time.
I texted you the address and the number.
Hope to see you soon.
Love you, bye.
Wild night, huh?
Yeah.
Who was that on the phone?
Girlfriend doesn't know
about your other life.
It was my sister, actually.
Even better.
I'm Erdy.
Jake.
Saw you in there.
You seemed to be having a good time.
How long you been coming here?
A while.
Yeah, me too.
I like it here.
You can pretty much find
anything you want here.
I like finding new people.
How come I didn't, uh...
How come I didn't see you
engaging with the others?
Sex really isn't my thing.
After a while,
your mind picks something
that really gets you
and itself off.
It sticks with it,
at least that's what I think anyway.
What's your thing?
Well,
you could follow me and find out.
Follow you where?
I got a place near here.
You wanna walk over there with me?
All right.
No, no this way.
Shelly, this is?
- Jake.
Jake, Shelly.
Oh, what a handsome young man.
Yeah, isn't he?
Can I get you anything, Jake?
Nah, I'm fine.
So, if you don't mind my asking,
what am I doing here?
Isn't it obvious?
You're gonna fuck my wife,
and I'm gonna watch.
Oh, he's shy.
Why don't you put on some music?
Great idea.
Anything in particular, Jake?
It's like the perfect balance
between joy and sadness.
Well,
Jake, let's get started.
You don't have to worry, Jake.
Nobody's gonna judge you here.
Now pull her to face me.
I wanna see my slut wife's face.
Pull her, pull her hair back.
Yeah.
Now start fucking her.
Hard.
Harder.
Fuck my slut wife harder.
Yeah.
Jake, look at you.
You didn't think a pill and a Coke
will keep me away for good, did you?
You know what you have to do.
Now go do it.
Go in and take a peek, Jake.
You know you want to.
Jake, don't feel guilty.
It's going to feel so good.
Awe, it's gonna be the ultimate high.
Hey.
Baby brother, hi.
You left the door open.
Yeah, I figured you might come.
How did you know?
Well, who wouldn't
wanna see his big sister
after two whole years.
How do I look?
You look good.
Yeah, I lost 10 pounds
since you last saw me.
Okay, let me go get changed.
I'll be right back.
Oh, my god!
I can't believe I'm finally
back in New York City.
She does look
good, doesn't she, Jake.
You should've taken a peek earlier.
I bet she looks good naked.
No, Jake, we're not going anywhere.
Don't even think about leaving.
We're too close now.
I tell you Colorado so boring.
I can't believe I moved
out there for that asshole.
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing I...
I just have a headache, all right.
Oh, okay.
Well,
come sit with me.
So, little brother, what's new with you?
Nothing much, just keeping busy.
Okay.
Did you fuck any cute girls lately?
What?
Were any of them as cute as me?
Why do you wanna know that?
You know why
she wants to know that?
It's just a question.
I'm sorry to hear that
you and Monica split up.
She was so pretty.
How long were you two together?
Eight months.
Wow, that's a pretty long time.
Well, I guess we're both single now
first me and Greg,
then you and Monica.
Why'd you guys break up anyway?
Let's talk about you.
What are you gonna do now
that you're back in the city?
I'm not sure.
Probably go try to get
laid, first and foremost.
See, I told you.
Are you fucking with me?
No.
Oh, wait, I almost forget.
I almost forget.
I got you something.
Happy belated birthday.
Thanks.
Well, open it.
Wanna know why it's blank?
So you can get started on the
next great American novel.
I don't write anymore.
Oh.
Really, why not?
I just lost the passion.
Well, I'm sure you'll find
something to do with it.
What did mom and dad give you?
Mom gave me money,
and dad he gave me his hunting knife.
Dad and his hunting.
Yeah, I bet he probably
missing you out there.
Look at her neck.
Doesn't that look good?
I'm so mixed up right now.
I should leave.
If I stay, something bad's gonna happen.
Jake, what do you mean?
I can't control myself.
Feel your dick getting hard?
Jake.
You want it.
You want it 'cause I want it.
You smell good.
Well, thank you.
But, Jake, you're really freaking me out.
Embrace it, embrace the high.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I'm really sorry I have to do this.
Do what?
Jake.
I just can't control myself.
What do you mean?
Jake.
I'm sorry I have to.
You have to understand.
I have to.
- Jake, what are you doing?
Jake.
Jake, stop it.
Jake!
Stop it, Jake!
Jake, get off!
Jake, stop it!
Jake!
Stop it, stop it!
Jake, stop it.
No.
I love Monica.
Fuck my wife.
You just blew us all off.
Everybody's got secrets.
Wanna fuck me?
What do you want?
Monica.
Monica, you in here?
Jake.
What are you doing here?
Monica.
I miss you.
Jake, you really shouldn't be here.
I have to tell you something.
You have to listen to me.
I'm fucked up.
All I think about is sex.
I can't stop it.
I've done some bad things.
Tonight I did something I can't take back.
I raped Molly.
What?
I don't know why I did it.
I can't help myself.
I can't control myself.
I think, I wanted to hurt myself.
Jake, I don't know what's going on,
and I don't know what you did.
But, you clearly need help,
and I can't be a part of it.
Monica, I don't feel anything anymore.
Jake, I have to go.
Are you okay, who is this guy?
It's just my ex.
No, I'm fine.
What's done is done, Jake.
Tomorrow you will wake up,
and we will do it all again
just like we always do.
This is who we are now.
Everybody's left you,
all these people in these photos,
everybody you've ever known,
everybody but me.
And I will always be
with you, Jake, always.